[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does active transport require the energy of the molecule adenosine diphosphate or ADP?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Using the apothecary system, how many grains are in 4 drams?", "correct_answer": "240", "incorrect_answers": ["200", "180", "220"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead, when the babysitter dies, the kids wrap her up in a rug and drag her to the trunk of the car.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about cortisol, a hormone produced by the cortex of the adrenal glands?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Makeup decreases cortisol levels.", "Lack of sleep increases cortisol levels.", "Caffeine increases cortisol levels."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these was introduced in Britain by Lady Mary Wortley, who was a prolific writer of diaries, essays and poems?", "correct_answer": "Smallpox innoculation", "incorrect_answers": ["The piano playing", "Musical modulation", "The literary salon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are Maryland\u2019s two official state nicknames?", "correct_answer": "\u201cThe Old Line State\u201d and \u201cThe Free State\u201d", "incorrect_answers": ["\u201cThe Crab State\u201d and \u201cOur Chesapeake Heritage\u201d", "\u201cThe Crab State\u201d and \u201cThe Old Line State\u201d", "\u201cThe Free State\u201d and \u201cOur Chesapeake Heritage\u201d"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If Kermit the Frog were a live animal, would he be considered an amphibian?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was/were the featured artist/group in Mad Dogs and Englishmen, a 1971 movie about an American music tour?", "correct_answer": "Joe Cocker", "incorrect_answers": ["Elton John", "The Commitments", "The Rolling Stones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the most popular casino games in the world, its precursor , vingt-et-un originated in French casinos around 1700.", "correct_answer": "Blackjack", "incorrect_answers": ["Bingo", "Roulette", "Two-up"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Southern rock musical group originally sang the song Sweet Home Alabama, which is also the theme song to the movie of the same name?", "correct_answer": "Lynyrd Skynyrd", "incorrect_answers": ["Molly Hatchet", "Chalie Daniels Band", "Alabama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The main characters from the movie Say Anything are Lloyd and Diane.  What are their last names?", "correct_answer": "Dobler and Court", "incorrect_answers": ["Dibler and Count", "Miller and Jones", "Brown and Green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actress delivered this movie line: You break my heart. Then again you break everyones heart.?", "correct_answer": "Demi Moore to Rob Lowe", "incorrect_answers": ["Jennifer Gray to Patrick Swayze", "Ally Sheedy to Judd Nelson", "Molly Ringwald to Judd Nelson"]}]